aboutone.com 2016-05-20

# Privacy Policy - AboutOne

  * Introduction
  * Privacy Policy
  * Collection of Personal Information from Site Users
  * Use of Personal Data Collected
  * Disclosure of Personal Data to Third Parties
  * Third Party Websites
  * Security Measures and Communicating with AboutOne
  * Opt-out Right
  * Access to and Ability to Correct Personal Data
  * Right to Change Privacy Policy
  * Children
  * Account Cancellation
  * Contacting AboutOne  

## 

## Introduction

Customer privacy and data security are paramount to AboutOne. AboutOne will not harvest your data and sell it.

We want our customers to know that we are committed to safeguarding their personal data. Privacy will always take center stage. AboutOne exceeds industry privacy standards and stays at the forefront of privacy on an international level.

The AboutOne consumer owns his or her own data; a user’s profile data is not shared with advertisers, partners, customers or even employees. Your data is always encrypted, and nobody can see it except YOU.

AboutOne, Inc. (“AboutOne”) has been awarded TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe’s program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/ "TRUSTe's Program Requirements") including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers information collected through these websites: www.aboutone.com and go.aboutone.com (hereafter referred to collectively as AboutOne.com). TRUSTe’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [support@aboutone.com](mailto:support@aboutone.com "Privacy Policy question from marketing website") or at 800-583-8537. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request).

AboutOne, Inc. complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from the from European Union member countries and Switzerland. AboutOne, Inc. has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view AboutOne’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Policy, you should first contact [support@aboutone.com](mailto:support@aboutone.com "Privacy Policy question from marketing website"). If contacting us does not resolve your complaint, you may raise your complaint with TRUSTe by [Internet here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request "Welcome to TRUSTe's Feedback and Resolution System"), or by fax at 415-520-3420 or mail to TRUSTe Safe Harbor Compliance Dept., [click for mailing address](http://www.truste.com/about-TRUSTe/contact-us "Contact TRUSTe"). If you are faxing or mailing TRUSTe to lodge a complaint, you must include the following information: the name of company, the alleged privacy violation, your contact information, and whether you would like the particulars of your complaint shared with the company. For information about TRUSTe or the operation of TRUSTe’s dispute resolution process, click [here](http://www.truste.com/products-and-services/dispute-resolution-services/ "TRUSTe Dispute Resolution Services") or request this information from TRUSTe at any of the addresses listed above. The TRUSTe dispute resolution process shall be conducted in English.

## 

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy applies to the services provided by aboutone.com, go.aboutone.com, and other various mobile applications owned and operated by AboutOne, Inc. (hereafter referred to collectively as AboutOne.com). This privacy policy describes how AboutOne, Inc. collects and uses the personal information you provide on our sites: aboutone.com, go.aboutone.com, and other various mobile applications (hereafter referred to collectively as AboutOne.com). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

AboutOne’s Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share and help you make informed decisions when using AboutOne, located at AboutOne.com. By using or accessing AboutOne, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

## 

## Collection of Personal Information from Site Users

You will be asked to provide your email address and your name when creating your AboutOne account.

Once you have registered, we collect other personal information about you in order to set up your account and serve you. You will be able to add additional information about yourself such as your name, gender, and marital status. You will be able to add information to your profile regarding your house (including the year it was built, size, bedrooms, phone number, date purchased, price, and the realtor). You may provide education information about yourself or your child (including the school attended and the type of education). You also have the option to upload a photo of yourself and each of your family members. **Please note that all content you enter or upload to the site cannot be viewed by anyone other than yourself or another user you choose as an administrator of your data (such as a spouse or caregiver).**

You are able to provide information about your family members as you start adding them to your profile. We collect your family members’ names, genders, relationships to you, and marital status. Adding information about yourself or family members is optional and you may correct, update or delete this information at any time. Please see “Access to and Ability to Correct Personal Data” section below.

If you sign up for our Plus, Premium, or Premium Plus service, we will collect your name, email address, and billing address. We use this information for the sole purpose of billing for your membership. Although we are PCI compliant, we do not store billing details; we leverage a third party provider (PayPal).

#### Your Birth Information

Within the Birth Information section of the site, you are able to enter your birth name, date of birth, weight, length, time of birth, blood type, eye color, hair color, where you were born, and the doctor who delivered you. You also have the option to upload a baby picture of yourself. We collect this information for the sole purpose of allowing you to store it within your profile and optionally print to a hard copy baby book.

#### Collecting Third Party Personal Information from Users

You have the opportunity to add contacts within your account. You can store their name, email address, date of birth, wedding anniversary, business contact information, photos, addresses, notes, and any linked documents. The AboutOne team does not have any access to this information and cannot use this information in any way. The information is collected for the sole purpose of allowing you to store it in your account.

#### Referrals

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. AboutOne stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us at [support@aboutone.com](mailto:support@aboutone.com "question from privacy policy page on marketing website") to request that we remove this information from our database.

Like many web sites, we may also automatically receive general information that is contained in our server log files such as your IP address and cookie information. Subject to the foregoing, AboutOne.com may collect or track (1) the home server domain names, type of client computer, files downloaded, search engine used, operating system, and type of Web browser of visitors to the Site, (2) information knowingly provided by the visitor in online forms, registration forms, e-mail, and other online avenues (including, without limitation, demographic and personal profile data), and (3) aggregate user-specific information regarding which pages Site visitors access.

#### Tracking Technologies / Cookies

AboutOne.com may place Internet “cookies” on visitors’ hard drives. Internet cookies save data about individual visitors, such as the visitor’s name, password, user-name, screen preferences, and the pages of a site viewed by the visitor. This information is collected solely for use when revisiting our site to ease data entry. No data will be shared. When the visitor revisits the site, AboutOne.com may recognize the visitor by the Internet cookie and customize the visitor’s experience accordingly. Visitors may decline Internet cookies, if any, by using the appropriate feature of their web client software, if available. When a visitor performs a search within AboutOne.com, AboutOne.com without limitation, may record information identifying the visitor or linking the visitor to the search performed such as their IP address. AboutOne.com may also record limited demographic information for every search request and use that information to solve technical problems with the services available directly or indirectly in connection with the Site and to calculate overall usage statistics.

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by AboutOne, Inc. and our marketing partners and analytics and online customer support service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for authentication and to remember users’ settings. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

#### Third Party Cookies

The use of cookies by third parties is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access to or control over these cookies. These third parties use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.

#### Log Files

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We do not use the logs for any purpose other than debugging server crashes. They are never linked to individual user information.

#### Local Storage Objects

Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site use LSOs such as HTML5 or Flash to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSAOs, please click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>

## 

## Use of Personal Data Collected

Personal data collected by AboutOne.com may be used by AboutOne.com for many reasons including to create a profile for you so that you may make use of our services, for editorial and feedback purposes, for marketing and promotional purposes, for statistical analysis of users’ behavior, for product development, for content improvement, for fulfillment of a requested transaction by a service provider, e.g. record keeping, or to customize the content and layout of the site. Aggregate data on visitors’ home servers may be used for internal purposes, and individually identifying information, such as names, postal and e-mail addresses, phone numbers, and other personal information which visitors voluntarily provide to AboutOne.com, may be added to AboutOne.com’s databases and used for future calls and mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, and upcoming events. AboutOne.com also may use site visitor data to contact the site visitors regarding account status and changes to the subscriber agreement (if applicable), Privacy Policy, and any other policies or agreements relevant to site visitors. AboutOne, Inc. employees do not have access to your individual data, but can run summarized user reports as a way to better offer you services. AboutOne, Inc. employees will never, under any circumstance, have access to any of the data in your AboutOne.com account.

#### Feedback

We use a third party service provider called Zendesk to host our feedback page. You may submit contact information, such as your name, address, telephone number, or email address, in connection with feedback, concerns, complaints, questions, or technical support. Such information is used only to respond to those inquiries and is governed by this Privacy Policy.

## 

## Disclosure of Personal Data to Third Parties

AboutOne, Inc. does not share, sell, rent or trade your individually identifiable information with third parties other than as disclosed within this privacy policy.

#### Agents/Service Providers

AboutOne, Inc. uses third party providers for email (to send product update emails), online chat, and billing services. When you sign up for our service, we will share your name and email address as necessary for the third party to provide that service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personal information for promotional purposes. Identifiable or non-identifiable data also may be disclosed or distributed to another party with which AboutOne, Inc. enters or reasonably may enter into a corporate transaction, such as a merger, consolidation, acquisition, or asset purchase, or to a third party pursuant to a subpoena, court order, or other form of legal process, in response to a request by or on behalf of any local, state, federal, or other government agency, department, or body, whether or not pursuant to a subpoena, court order, or other form of legal process, or if determined by AboutOne, Inc. in its sole judgment that such disclosure or distribution is appropriate to protect the life, health, or property of AboutOne, Inc. or any other person or entity. AboutOne, Inc. will undertake efforts to see that any third party with which AboutOne, Inc. shares or otherwise discloses personal data is under an obligation to use the personal data solely for the purposes for which the data was disclosed.

#### Legal Disclaimer

If AboutOne, Inc. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information and to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

#### Shareables

AboutOne Inc. may offer you a way to share information with third-party websites, such as social media websites, and other individuals who may or may not be an AboutOne.com account holder. The items that potentially could be shared include but are not limited to: memories, pictures, videos, events, and other user-created items/entries within AboutOne.com. You, the account holder, maintain sole responsibility and liability for the information you choose to share. The use of AboutOne, Inc.’s Shareables feature is optional and you, the account holder, have control over what information is shared, when it is shared, and with whom it is shared. AboutOne, Inc. assumes NO responsibility or liability for any information you have shared, or the actions taken by third-party websites or individuals after your information has been shared with them.

## 

## Third Party Websites

This site may contain links to other web sites or advertisements for or placed by third parties. AboutOne.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such web sites, advertisers, or third parties, nor for the content of such sites or advertisements. It is possible that these links or advertisements, themselves, may be used by third parties or others to collect personal or other information about site visitors. It is solely the visitor’s obligation to review and understand the privacy practices and policies of these other web sites and of these advertisers and third parties.

#### Blogs

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [support@aboutone.com](mailto:support@aboutone.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

#### Testimonials

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [support@aboutone.com](mailto:support@aboutone.com).

#### Social Media Widgets

Our website includes Social Media Widgets, such as the Share button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

#### Single Sign-On

You can login to our site using sing-in services such as Google. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with use. These services may also give you the option to post information about your activities on this website to their service to share with others within your network.

#### Import Contacts and Events

You can import contacts from your Facebook, Google and Outlook-formatted CSV files into AboutOne.com for the purpose of easily accessing their contact information in one place. We do not invite them to become members of our site unless you explicitly share content with them. We do not obtain the username and password for the email account from which you import your contacts and events. Imported events are analyzed in order to categorize and properly display them in your account. Events will not be shared with others unless you explicitly do so.

## 

## Security Measures and Communicating with AboutOne

AboutOne, Inc. has implemented numerous security features that are designed to prevent the unauthorized release of or access to personal information. AboutOne.com maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal laws to guard your nonpublic personal information. AboutOne.com is not responsible for the security of information transmitted via the Internet and no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. Instead of communicating with AboutOne via e-mail ([support@aboutone.com](mailto:support@aboutone.com)) or the Internet, visitors can contact AboutOne by regular mail at AboutOne, Inc. 23 N. Walnut Street, West Chester, PA 19380 or at 800-583-8537.

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter personal information and sensitive information such as credit card information on our site, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

## 

## Opt-Out Right

Except as necessary for AboutOne to provide the services, information, or products requested by a visitor, you may opt out of having your personal information, which has been voluntarily provided to AboutOne.com through online forms, registration forms, e-mail, or another online avenue, prospectively retained by AboutOne, used by AboutOne for secondary purposes (including those in Section “Use of Personal Data” above), by contacting AboutOne via postal mail, e-mail, or telephone at the addresses set out in the Security Measures and Communicating with AboutOne section above.

## 

## Access to and Ability to Correct Personal Data

Upon a visitor’s request via postal mail, e-mail, or telephone, AboutOne will provide to the visitor a summary of any personal information retained by AboutOne.com regarding the visitor that has been voluntarily provided by the visitor to AboutOne.com through online forms, registration forms, surveys, e-mail, or another online avenue. A visitor may modify, correct, change, delete or update his or her personal information by contacting AboutOne via postal mail, e-mail, or telephone at the addresses or numbers above. You may request deletion of your e-mail address by contacting our webmaster at [support@aboutone.com](mailto:support@aboutone.com). Other data that you have provided to us will continue to remain within our files at our discretion even though your e-mail is deleted. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

Information you choose to track in the AboutOne.com application such as personal information, family members’ personal information, education information, photos and more are not tracked in any way by AboutOne. It is for the sole purpose of the user. If you choose to modify, correct, change or delete any of this information, you can easily do so from within the application AboutOne.com.

#### Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [support@aboutone.com](mailto:support@aboutone.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

#### Newsletter

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page, or you can contact us at [support@aboutone.com](mailto:support@aboutone.com "Privacy Policy question from marketing website")

## 

## Right to Change Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy policy, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the change becoming effective.

## 

## Children

Please be aware that the site is a general audience web site, not directed to children under the age of 18, and must not be used by children under 18. We do not knowingly collect individually identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18.

## 

## Account Cancellation

To close your account, complete the cancellation form here: <http://aboutone.wufoo.com/forms/account-cancelation/>. Once we receive your form, we will close your account and send you a confirmation. The account cancellation process deletes all data in the account. Please be sure you have downloaded all data prior to submitting the cancellation form.

## 

## Contacting AboutOne

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with the site, please call us at 800-583-853, or contact us at AboutOne, Inc., 23 N. Walnut Street, West Chester, PA 19380 or via email at [support@aboutone.com](mailto:support@aboutone.com "Privacy Policy question from marketing website").

_Last updated: February  23, 2015, AboutOne, Inc.; All rights reserved._
